(Raj:)I don't care.
(Raj:)And why don't you think
I can find a woman for myself?
You're 27, the closest thing
we have...
(Mrs Koothrappali:)... to a daughter-in-law
is that Jewish boy, Howard.
(Raj:)Oh, that is completely below the belt.
(Raj:)Sheldon, tell my parents
that Howard and I are just friends.
(Leonard:)Sheldon?
(Raj:)Howard and I are just friends.
(Raj:)Fine. I'll come home
for Sanjay's wedding.
(Penny:)Sheldon.
[WHISTLES]
(Leonard:)What are you doing?
He's not a lost dog.
(Penny:)Hey, why don't you just let me find him...
(Penny:)...while you sit there
hitting your imaginary brake?
(Leonard:)The brake might be imaginary,
but that stop sign you just ran wasn't.
(Penny:)-What stop sign?
-Eyes on the road. Eyes on the road!
[DOORBELL RINGS]
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Howard, answer the door! I'm busy!